Contact

0543822181 (Mobile) samuelawuro@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/samuelawuro (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Git

GitHub

Team Leadership

Certifications

Allied Health Professions Council Registered Radiographer

Honors-Awards

Most Promising male graduating student in Diagnostic Radiography, 2020

Samuel Awuro Sampuo

Diagnostic Radiographer | Student @ALX Africa Accra, Greater Accra Region, Ghana

Summary

I am diagnostic radiographer with 3 years of clinical based experience and proficiency in general conventional imaging (Computed and Digital Radiography), Computed Tomography, CT (that includes specialized procedures as CT angiography) and MRI. Fascinated by Technology, I joined the ALX Africa program to become abreast of Technological skills that can empower me to lead in Tech and to learn about the various ways Africa is leveraging Technology to improve healthcare and provide jobs for the youth in the Sub-Saharan.

#ThefutureisTech

Experience

First American specialist Medical Center, Ghana Diagnostic Radiographer October 2023 - Present (10 months) Greater Accra Region, Ghana

alx_africa
Student
March 2024 - Present (5 months)

Totalité Health Limited Lead Diagnostic Radiographer September 2021 - August 2023 (2 years) Kumasi, Ashanti, Ghana

Zabzugu District Hospital
Diagnostic Radiographer
October 2020 - September 2021 (1 year)
Zabzugu-Tatale District, Northern, Ghana

Education

University of Ghana

Bsc Diagnostic Radiography, Medicine · (August 2016 - July 2020)